const tempData = 
{
  "questions": 
  [
    {
      "category": "Heights",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "Which mountain is the highest point on Earth from sea level?",
          "answer": "Mount Everest"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the tallest building in the world (as of 2020)?",
          "answer": "Burj Khalifa"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "How tall is a penny standing on it's edge (in in.)",
          "answer": "0.75 in"
        },
        {
          "question": "How tall is the NBA regulation basketball rim height (in ft) ",
          "answer": "10 ft"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What height (in km) is the Kármán Line at?",
          "answer": "100 km"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What year did WWI begin?",
          "answer": "1914"
        },
        {
          "question": "What year did the first moon landing occur?",
          "answer": "1969"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What year was the first FIFA World Cup tournament held?",
          "answer": "1930"
        },
        {
          "question": "What year did Pan Am go out of business?",
          "answer": "1991"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "How long (in days) did the Emu War last?",
          "answer": "39 days"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Literature",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "Who was the author of the poem Iliad?",
          "answer": "Homer"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in Joanne Rowling's most notable book series?",
          "answer": "Harry Potter"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "Which Japanese theoretical physicist is well known for his one of his bestsellers, 'Physics of the Impossible'?",
          "answer": "Michio Kaku"
        },
        {
          "question": "How many circles of hell is traversed in Inferno (Dante)?",
          "answer": "9"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "Who was the author of the play, 'Of Mice and Men'?",
          "answer": "John Steinbeck"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Games",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is commonly referred to as the first video game?",
          "answer": "Pong"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of a tile matching game that contains a move known as a 'T-spin'?",
          "answer": "Tetris"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the franchise based on military science fiction, with an intersetellar war between humanity and the Covenant?",
          "answer": "Halo"
        },
        {
          "question": "What type of weapon does Squall wield in the Final Fantasy series?",
          "answer": "Gunblade"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "How tall is Mario (in cm)?",
          "answer": "155 cm"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "Where is the capital city of Australia?",
          "answer": "Canberra"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the city-state in Italy?",
          "answer": "Vatican City"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the region bounded by Hawaii, New Zealand, and Easter Island called?",
          "answer": "Polynesia"
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does the Haka dance originate from?",
          "answer": "New Zealand"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the cold current that flows North, along the western coast of South America?",
          "answer": "Humboldt Current"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is a saccharide more commonly known as?",
          "answer": "Sugar"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
          "answer": "Mitochondria"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the term used to describe smooth or regular fluid flow?",
          "answer": "Laminar Flow"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the random motion of particles suspended in a medium known as?",
          "answer": "Brownian Motion"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the subatomic particle that make up hadrons?",
          "answer": "Quark"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Technology",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the counting tool used in ancient times as a calculator?",
          "answer": "Abacus"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the machine used by Nazi Germany to encrypt communication?",
          "answer": "Enigma machine"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the creator of the Linux kernel?",
          "answer": "Linus Torvalds"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the computer produced by a company with a raspberry logo?",
          "answer": "Raspberry Pi"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "The first macOS released during which year?",
          "answer": "2001"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Weight",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "How many pounds (lbs) are there to 1 kilogram (kg), to 1 decimal point?",
          "answer": "2.2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Roughly how much does 1 liter of water weigh, in kilograms (kg)?",
          "answer": "1 kg"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "1 kilogram (kg) of feathers weighs the same as how many kilograms (kg) of metal?",
          "answer": "1 kg"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the average weight of a car in 2018, to the nearest 1000 lbs?",
          "answer": "4000 lbs"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What is the weight limit (in lbs) of intermodal freight containers?",
          "answer": "42500 lbs"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Social Media",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Google's social network launched in 2011?",
          "answer": "Google+"
        },
        {
          "question": "Tom Anderson founded this social networking service in 2003.",
          "answer": "MySpace"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What social networking service refers to user's posts as 'tweets'?",
          "answer": "Twitter"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which city was LinkedIn founded in?",
          "answer": "Mountain View"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What app did Facebook acquire in 2014 for 19 billion dollars?",
          "answer": "WhatsApp"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Movies",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the 2010 science fiction action film directed by Christopher Nolan?",
          "answer": "Inception"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the full name of the movie in which an infamous Killer Rabbit of Caerbannog appears?",
          "answer": "Monty Python and the Holy Grail"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "Hello. My name is ________. You killed my father. Prepare to die.",
          "answer": "Inigo Montoya"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the full name of the character Jim Carrey played in 'The Truman Show'?",
          "answer": "Truman Burbank"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What is Mrs. Doubtfire's real name in the movie, 'Mrs. Doubtfire'?",
          "answer": "Daniel Hillard"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Statues",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What color was the Statue of Liberty originally?",
          "answer": "Copper"
        },
        {
          "question": "What city is the statue, 'Christ the Redeemer' located in?",
          "answer": "Rio De Janeiro"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the animal depicted by this statue near the Pyramids?",
          "answer": "Sphinx"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who sculpted the masterpiece, 'David', out of white marble?",
          "answer": "Michelangelo"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What is the well known army of buried clay soldiers in Xi'an, China, made out of?",
          "answer": "Terracotta"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Duos",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What are the names of the cat and mouse duo in their iconic cartoon series, named after themselves?",
          "answer": "Tom and Jerry"
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the names of the superhero and sidekick duo that have names alluding to flying animals?",
          "answer": "Batman and Robin"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the folk rock duo that released 'The Sound of Silence'?",
          "answer": "Simon and Garfunkel"
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the first names of the Weasley twins in the Harry Potter series (alphabetically)?",
          "answer": "Fred and George"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "What are the names of the iconic duo of the 'Back to the Future' series?",
          "answer": "Marty McFly and Doc Brown"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "S",
      "easy": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of a watercraft capable of independent operation underwater?",
          "answer": "Submarine"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which word refers to words or phrases that mean exactly or nearly the same as another word?",
          "answer": "Synonym"
        }
      ],
      "medium": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the famous song by Led Zeppelin, released in 1971, with a length of just over 8 minutes?",
          "answer": "Stairway to Heaven"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the term used to describe the use of irony to mock or convey contempt?",
          "answer": "Sarcasm"
        }
      ],
      "hard": [
        {
          "question": "Who played Robert 'Rocky' Balboa in the 1976 film 'Rocky'?",
          "answer": "Sylvester Stallone"
        }
      ]
    },
  ]
};

export default tempData;
